The work quickly
escalated into his
terrifying climb while
his team drilled
into the ground
below. He stood
alone on a
towering pillar high
above the tiles.
The blue sky,
the only witness
to his isolation.
Something shifted when
he asked, who
was there? The
ground floor felt
like a different
world, distant and
cold. He felt
trapped, unable to
leave, as if
invisible hands were
holding him in
place. The tools
scattered below didn't
feel like equipment
anymore. They felt
like evidence of
a crime. Every
drill sound echoing
up to him
was a heartbeat
of a machine
trying to cut
him off. He
saw the long
gray beam being
cut while he
hung suspended. A
giant saw slicing
through his safety.
The structure swayed
slightly as he
drilled into the
vertical member, terrified
to miss a
single millimeter. Was
he repairing a
building or holding
back a collapsing
tower? The air
grew heavy, pressing
down on him.
He looked down
at the workers,
but they seemed
for...